

MD. ABDUN NAHID



PERSONAL SUMMARY

Enthusiastic diligent web developer with experience and exceptional knowledge on innovative up-to-date web development technologies: **Angular**, **Node Js**. Also skilled with **lonic**- a cross platform mobile application development technology.

Collaborator with the ability to adopt challenging environment easily. Have excellent critical thinking skills and fast learning capability. Usual to take on new challenges and turn them into opportunities.

Equipped with strong work ethics. Always try to provide the best work and professionalism.



EDUCATION

Computer Science & Engineering | University of Liberal Arts Bangladesh

2014 - 2018

CGPA - 3.84 on a scale of 4.00

Award - Cum Laude



EXPERIENCE

Arbree Limited | Web & Cross Platform Mobile App Developer

May 2018 – Present

Link: https://www.arbree.com/

Arbree Limited | Intern

Feb 2018 - Apr 2018



SKILLS

Programming Languages

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Node.js

Frameworks & Libraries

- Angular
- Ionic
- Express.js
- Angular Material
- Bootstrap



Arbree Attendance | Web, PWA & Android, IOS

Technologies: Angular 7, Ionic 3, Cordova, Google Firebase, Cloud Firestore

A complete Attendance Solution that helps managing workforce and track employee time and attendance in an easier, more efficient way.

Link: https://www.arbree.com/

Link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.arbree.arbreeattendance

Arbree | Web & Mobile Application

Technologies: AngularJs, Ionic-Cordova, .NET Core, SQL, SignalR

A project management tool that provides a wide range of features to manage company. file sharing. Creating projects, manage team meetings, access archived database and advanced search are some of the features to mention.

Link: https://www.arbree.com:90/

Soldiers Leave Management | Web Application

Technologies: Angular 7, .NET Core, SQL

A leave management software built for soldiers of Border Guard Bangladesh (BGB).

Demo Link: https://soldiers-leave.firebaseapp.com



OPEN SOURCE

Material Date Picker | Angular Component

Technologies: Angular, TypeScript

A date picker is built for Angular Applications as angular component. The picker can pick single, multiple and range type of dates easily with a beautiful graphical user interface.

NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/ngx-aaa-datepicker GUTHUB: https://github.com/Nahid-Rezvee/ngx-aaa-datepicker

Express CLI | ExpressJs App Boilerplates Generator

Technologies: NodeJS

This is a cli tool that helps develop rest API based express.js applications help creating new project and generating different modules (Ex: Route, Model, Middleware) by following standard express.js project architecture.

NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/@nahidrezvee/express-cli

GUTHUB: https://github.com/Nahid-Rezvee/nahidx



SDG Hackathon | Code for a Cause

Hackathon

Participated on the "SDG Hackathon 2018" organized by Google Developers Group Bangladesh & Banglalink. Our team was one of the top ten teams.

Hacker Rank | **Problem Solving**

Problem Solver

I am a problem solver in "Hacker Rank", a problem solving and programming contest site.

Profile: https://www.hackerrank.com/abdun nahid

Certificate of Participation | CISCO Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

Workshop

Certified "Network Associate". Completed an 8 hours Networking course jointly organized by ADN EDUSERVICE LIMITED | ULAB

Certificate of Participation | Global Career in Project Management

Workshop

Participated in a Workshop on "Global Career in Project Management" on 12 August, 17 Organized by *PMASPIRE LIMITED | Professional Development Unit*

Certificate of Participation | CSE Fest 2016

App Idea Contest

Participated in a Contest named "App Idea Contest" on "CSE Fest 2016" Organized by *Computer Programming Club & IEEE | ULAB*

Certificate of Participation | Perspective Career in Programming

Workshop

Participated in a Workshop on "Perspective Career in Programming" on 21 May, 15 Organized by *Khairul Islam | Founder of Lollypop Lab*

Photographer | Bangladesh Shilpakala Academy

Photo Exhibition on "Pollyanna"

Participated on a photo exhibition titled "Pollyanna" on "Bangladesh Shilpakala Academy" | National Cultural Center of Bangladesh. Two of my photos had been selected for the exhibition.

Photography Portfolio: https://www.istockphoto.com/portfolio/nahid



REFERENCES

Zahidul Islam

Lead Mobile Application Developer
Arbree Limited
Email: engg.zahidulislam@gmail.com

Anwarul Islam Rana

*Lead Back end developer*Arbree Limited

Email: anwarul.i@hotmail.com